{
    "id": "44c94850d8884381a9cedec8dbd19e15",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Will you please wait here ................................. I come back?",
            "description": "Both till and until are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will come and see you ........................... I can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be in bed ........................ the time you get back.",
            "description": "Note the expression 'by the time'.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ............................. I have the information.",
            "description": "Both 'when' and 'as soon as' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "when",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be relieved ............................ it is finished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to finish it ........................ you can leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "when",
                "before",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I scraped my knee ............................. I was playing football.",
            "description": "Either 'while' or 'when' is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "when",
                "whenever"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I injure myself .............................. I play football.",
            "description": "Either 'when' or 'whenever' are possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "whenever",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you the message ............................. I receive it.",
            "description": "The expression 'the moment' can mean 'as soon as'.",
            "answers": [
                "a moment",
                "the moment"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be ready when you ..........................",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to future. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will do it only ............................ you pay me.",
            "description": "We use 'if' to indicate condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped playing .............................. it started raining.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. Because of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}